# MAULIK THAKRAR

## **Android Developer**

EXPERIENCE

### Android Developer

ZetrixWeb Infotech LLP 12/2021 - 06/2022 Ahmedabad (WFH)

- My role is to design, develop and test the application that meet the requirements of our mocks and fulfill our user stories.
- · Worked with Android JUnit Extensions for writing test cases.
- Wrote unit tests for mobile code and debugged critical application issues such as crashes, and memory leaks.
- Tested code for robustness; executed edge case, usability, and general reliability analysis.
- · Fixed bugs and improved application performance.
- Developed native Android applications and also Implemented features for various applications in Java and Kotlin.

## Android Developer

Jogi infotech 06/2018 - 11/2021 Junagadh

- · I have also worked on ongoing projects'.
- Lead 7 mobile developers in the design and development of E-commerce app.

## Android Developer

Sanskartechnolab pvt Ltd 10/2016 - 05/2018 Junagadh

- Independently handled modules, scope, analysis, design, build, test the code, debug and implement application. Independently handled modules, scope, analysis, design, build, test the code, debug and implement application.
- Independently handled modules, scope, analysis, design, build, test the code, debug and implement application.
- · Fixed bugs and improved application performance.
- Launched Android app that maintains a 4/5 star rating in the Google Play store with 5k+ downloads.

PROJECTS

#### PushtiSanskar

https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.sanskar.pushtisanskar App contains use full resources and contents related to Pushti Marg and Shree Vallabh.

#### EzBee

https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=in.ezbee.store
Online shop for grocery, fruits, vegetables and all your home needs.

## Shreeji Credit

 $\label{lem:https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.shreejicredit.memberapp Financial support app. \\$ 

#### The MealDeal

https://themealdeal.in/

Coupons Web Site(User, Admin and Restaurant modules In Laravel)

#### SUMMARY

I am an experienced Android developer having more than five years of active Android development.

I have worked on numerous projects such as Religious apps, E-commerce apps, educational apps, social apps, Restaurant apps, and many more.

Implemented features for various applications in Java and Kotlin.

SKILLS

Designing, developing, testing

**API** integration

Firebase Push Notifications.

Google Map, Location API.

In-App Purchase.

**Payment Gateway Integrations** 

LANGUAGES

Kotlin

Java

**EDUCATION** 

M.C.A

Dr. Subhash College, Junagadh( G.T.U) 05/2016

STRENGTHS

Get things done

🟁 Focusing on aim

Problem Solving